<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="en">
	<title>Secret Choir</title>
	<subtitle>A music blog, built with Octobug</subtitle>
	<link href="https://secretchoir.com/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://secretchoir.com/"/>
	<updated>2025-01-15T08:03:59Z</updated>
	<id>https://secretchoir.com/</id>
	<author>
		<name>Casey K</name>
		<email>casey@kolderup.org</email>
	</author>
		
		<entry>
			<title>2024 You Could Make a Case For: Durante - _Enter_</title>
			<link href="https://secretchoir.com/post/1736927939285/"/>
			<updated>2025-01-15T07:58:59Z</updated>
			<id>https://secretchoir.com/post/1736927939285/</id>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<div>
				<p><a href="https://durante.bandcamp.com/album/enter">https://durante.bandcamp.com/album/enter</a></p>
<p>the "You Could Make a Case For" series is for albums that did not spring to mind for me immediately, but when reviewing the stuff I did actually listen to this year, I noticed them as things that I definitely did find myself pressing play on during the course of the year.</p>
<p>I first learned about Durante via the 2019 Fabric DJ mix by electronic artist Bonobo, an album I listened to constantly both by myself and when putting on music for other people. His track "Maia" swoops in beautifully and while he didn't have many tracks released at that point, I was excited eventually to discover his 2021 song "Thread Tension", a driving, hypnotic track. There were some releases here and there but it was this year's <em>Enter</em> and the accompanying <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nWdIkR-6Vio">February</a> and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vh246_Mgk7o">May</a> DJ mixes that I could tell there was something special he was doing, creating a sound I'm really glad to have had available to me this year.</p>

					<p>Tagged:
							<a href="/tags/2024/">#2024</a>, 
							<a href="/tags/you-could-make-a-case-for/">#you could make a case for</a>
					</p>
			</div>]]></content>
		</entry>
		
		<entry>
			<title>2024 Safe Bets: Vegyn - _The Road to Hell is Paved with Good Intentions_</title>
			<link href="https://secretchoir.com/post/1736924679776/"/>
			<updated>2025-01-15T07:04:39Z</updated>
			<id>https://secretchoir.com/post/1736924679776/</id>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<div>
				<p><a href="https://vegyn.bandcamp.com/album/the-road-to-hell-is-paved-with-good-intentions">https://vegyn.bandcamp.com/album/the-road-to-hell-is-paved-with-good-intentions</a></p>
<p>I dunno what to say about this one, it just is the mood I felt in the most this year. I felt ready to put this on just about any time-- as a plane was landing, when I couldn't sleep, when I had a quiet afternoon sitting around peacefully with my parents in my new living room, when I was walking around a new part of San Francisco I had never been in before (near the Moscone Center? lol), just any time really. I guess that makes it the next in a series:</p>
<p>2024 - this one<br>
2023 - overmono - good lies<br>
2022 - sadurn - radiator<br>
2021 - ross from friends - tread<br>
2020 - cartalk - pass like pollen<br>
2019 - glass beach - the first glass beach album</p>

					<p>Tagged:
							<a href="/tags/2024/">#2024</a>, 
							<a href="/tags/safe-bets/">#safe bets</a>
					</p>
			</div>]]></content>
		</entry>
		
		<entry>
			<title>2024 Safe Bets: Vampire Weekend - _Only God Was Above Us_</title>
			<link href="https://secretchoir.com/post/1736923909329/"/>
			<updated>2025-01-15T06:51:49Z</updated>
			<id>https://secretchoir.com/post/1736923909329/</id>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<div>
				<p><a href="https://us.7digital.com/artist/vampire-weekend/release/only-god-was-above-us-explicit-39422357">https://us.7digital.com/artist/vampire-weekend/release/only-god-was-above-us-explicit-39422357</a></p>
<p>I had very complicated feelings about <em>Father of the Bride</em>, though ultimately came out pretty positive about it. I do feel like this is a return to <em>Modern Vampires</em> success but also I feel a little bit guilty about feeling that way because of the <em>signifiers</em></p>

					<p>Tagged:
							<a href="/tags/safe-bets/">#safe bets</a>, 
							<a href="/tags/2024/">#2024</a>
					</p>
			</div>]]></content>
		</entry>
		
		<entry>
			<title>2024 Safe Bets: Saeph - _Verdant_</title>
			<link href="https://secretchoir.com/post/1736923709481/"/>
			<updated>2025-01-15T06:48:29Z</updated>
			<id>https://secretchoir.com/post/1736923709481/</id>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<div>
				<p><a href="https://saeph.bandcamp.com/album/verdant">https://saeph.bandcamp.com/album/verdant</a></p>
<p>Listening to this album does make me feel alive-- alive because I can hear the influences from Porter Robinson and Madeon, from chiptunes to blasted out VHS copies of anime series you've never remembered the title of recovered from a friends of the library table sale. Listen to this album if you're a little goblin in the forest in an RPG Maker game</p>

					<p>Tagged:
							<a href="/tags/2024/">#2024</a>, 
							<a href="/tags/safe-bets/">#safe bets</a>
					</p>
			</div>]]></content>
		</entry>
</feed>
